Ah, hello.
あ、こんにちは
That's a lot.
多いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's pure white.
真っ白じゃん
It suits you.
似合うね
You usually wear it, right?
普段着てるでしょ?
What does your regular uniform look like?
普段の制服はどんな感じ?
Usually a sailor.
普段はセーラー
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
What do you think, are you wearing it now?
どうですか、今着てるの?
cute.
かわいい
How old are you now?
何歳、今?
It's 18.
18です
How old are you?
何年生?
That's right.
ですね
Are you graduating soon?
もうすぐ卒業?
perhaps.
多分
Do you think you can graduate?
卒業できそう?
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Is there a possibility of remorse?
留念の可能性がある?
No, An-chan.
いや、あんちゃん
You better study, quickly.
勉強した方がいいよ、早く
Something.
なんか
Sorry, kind of.
ごめんね、なんか
I called you.
呼び出しちゃって
not at all.
全然
I'll study for you.
勉強しててあげるから
What do you dislike most?
何が一番苦手?
math?
数学?
I thought so.
だと思った
Everyone is not good at it.
みんな苦手なんだよ
Aren't you going to take university entrance exams?
大学受験とかはしない?
If I can graduate, I want to go to university.
卒業できるなら大学行きたいなって
If you were thinking about taking the exam, you'd still be doing it.
受験考えてたら今もやってるよね
I'm studying.
勉強してます
Are you studying?
勉強してる?
TRUE?
本当?
I'm studying.
勉強してる
So, you haven't decided on your dream career yet?
じゃあ夢、進路は決めてない?
Want to make money?
お金稼ぎたい?
Yeah.
うん
Then you'd better study.
じゃあ勉強した方がいいよ
Let's do our best and go to university.
頑張って大学行こうぜ
I'll wake you up a bit today.
今日はちょっと起こすから
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけどね
I even went home before.
前も帰るくらい
I did it.
やった
Just a little today.
ちょっとさ、今日は
Let me take a picture.
ちょっと 撮らせて
Don't you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいない?
I have a boyfriend.
彼氏はいます
Are you there?
いる?
That's nice.
いいですね
Is it the same school?
それは同じ学校?
classmate?
同級生?
Same class.
同じクラス
Is that so?
そうなの?
I couldn't help but smile a little.
ちょっと笑顔がこぼれちゃいました
Do you have sex?
エッチとかするの?
Do you want to?
するか?
Yeah.
うん
As expected?
さすがに?
As expected.
さすがに
picture?
え?
Was it your first time?
初めてしたの?
How old are you?
何歳くらい?
First time...
初めては...
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are you currently dating a boyfriend?
今付き合ってる彼氏?
Not.
じゃない
The boyfriend you were dating at the time?
当時付き合ってた彼氏?
He's not an old man.
おじさんじゃないよ
Isn't that your uncle?
おじさんじゃない?
A school teacher?
学校の先生?
A senior at my part-time job?
バイトの先輩?
You're a university student, right?
大学生でしょ?
university student?
大学生?
university student.
大学生
Because I'll eat it.
食うから
Oh, that was cool?
あ、かっこよかった?
Okay then.
じゃあいいじゃん
That's good.
よかったじゃん
What do you do part-time?
何のバイトしてるの?
I'm currently working part-time at a cafe.
今はカフェでバイトしてます
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
busy?
忙しい?
Isn't it held in May?
5月とかやってない?
In May...
5月は...
I quit.
やめちゃった
Did you quit?
やめた?
How many minutes?
何分?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Did you quit because you wanted to hang out with your boyfriend?
彼氏と遊びたいからやめたの?
There were so many things I wanted to do.
やりたいこといっぱいあったから
I'll teach you a lot of things.
いろいろ教えてあげるね
so?
そんなに?
do you have it?
持ってるの?
Yeah.
うん
Well, let's just have sex once.
じゃあ ちょっとセックス一回で
Because I lost.
負けちゃったから
surely.
確かに
I'm at the age where I laugh at everything I do.
何やっても笑う年頃なんだね
You didn't even notice.
気づいてさえなかったよね
That's interesting.
面白いね
A long time ago, I liked uniforms so much that I looked at them a little too closely.
昔さ、制服姿好きすぎてさ、 ちょっとまじまじ見すぎてて、
I was forced to quit because I looked cool.
格好してやめさせられた
Oh no.
やば
This is cute.
可愛いね、これ
Is this it?
これかな?
Don't you want to be seen like this?
こうやって見られたいとかしない?
I think this is the only way to look at it.
こうやって見るしかないと思うけど
Don't you want to be seen?
見られたいとかしない?
this.
これ
Let's flip through this for a moment.
ちょっとこれ、こうやってめくってみる
this?
これ?
He's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いやつ
The whole thing, right?
全体でしょ?
Yeah.
うん
There's nothing I can do, and there's nothing I can do about it.
どうしようもないし、 どうしようもないから
It's amazing today.
今日すごいね
What not?
どうしない?
I don't care.
どうでもいいし
Are your eyes big?
目が大きい?
About B.
Bくらい
About B?
Bくらい?
Is there a possibility that it is E?
もしかしたらEの可能性もある?
Yeah.
うん
possibility,
可能性、
There are also creatures of possibility.
可能 性の生き物もある
I don't know because I haven't studied it.
勉強してないからわかんない
Just a little bit.
わざわざ、ちょっと
I don't know because I'm not studying.
勉強じゃないからわかんない
I'm just not good at it.
ちょっと、得意じゃないですよ
I'm not good at it, but I'm not good at other things either.
得意じゃないけど、 他にも得意じゃない
picture?
え?
history.
歴史
So, do you want to teach me?
じゃあ、教えたり?
Health and sports.
保健体育
You seem good at it, right?
得意そうでしょ?
Health and sports.
保健体育
Success.
成功ね
I can't get it no matter what.
どうしてもらえない
Her lower body is cute.
下身可愛いもんね
I end up leaving the upper part alone.
上 のところを込めて残すタイプになってしまう
I'll leave some things that are different.
違うところも残しちゃう
My father was successful in this regard.
これにとっては親父がうまくいって
Really.
本当にね
That's interesting.
面白いね
I really think so.
本当に思ってるね
You have a matching body.
一致な体をしてるね
I tend to get embarrassed when people stare at me.
見つめられると照れるほう
Because your shy face is cute.
照れてる顔かわいいから
It's really impossible.
本当 に 無理です
So it doesn't fall.
だから落ちかない
People who kiss are also bad.
キスつきの人も悪いですよね
I wondered what he was saying when he said that too.
俺も言ってて何言ってるんだろうと思った
Bandai,
バンダイして、
It will never break.
絶 対切れない
Damn it.
ちげえぞ
Hey, it's a little too cute to be successful.
めねえ、ちょっと成功かわいいむらい
Please bring it on.
つけてきてくれな
Disease physical education.
疾患体育
Successful sports.
成功体育
I don't know.
分かんない
It's not something you should listen to while being pranked.
ちちぷにぷにされながら聞くことじゃない
After all, it's the nipples.
やっぱら乳首とかさ
Where is it?
どこだろう?
2 experienced leads?
経験リード2人?
With my boyfriend?
彼氏と?
Don't know about encounters?
出会いが知らない?
I don't know about the encounter.
出会いが知らない
S
シ
Mi is completed.
ミ ができてます
There are stains.
シミができてる
There's no way you'll get wet enough to get a stain just from kissing and boobs.
キスとおっぱいだけで、 シミできるほど濡れるわけないよね
Easy to feel.
感じやすい
Very occasionally.
めっちゃたまに
Are you saying you're going to do it?
めっちゃするって言うの?
I do it very occasionally.
めっちゃたまにするんだ
How do you do it then?
それ時はどうやってするの?
refer to?
指?
Can you buy it?
買えないか
I can't go shopping.
買いに行けない
Okay.
いいよ
I have to take a good look and confirm.
きれいに見て確認しないといけない
By myself.
自分でさ
I get compliments on my butt.
お尻褒められる
I've been praised before.
褒められたことある
Your butt has a really nice shape.
お尻ほんときれいな形してるね
My butt is no longer wet.
お尻ひょうるんこなくなった
My shoulders are down and my butt is down.
肩がきょういんで、お尻
Right?
でしょ?
With such a white and beautiful butt,
こんだけ白くてきれいなお尻だと、
I don't want to hit you.
たたきたくない
It's so squishy.
ぷにぷにしてますね
That's a compliment.
これ褒め言葉よ
My pussy is squishy.
おまんこがぷにぷにしてる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Isn't there a man who can compliment you there?
そこ褒めてくれる男いない?
I can't show it.
見せない
Yes, take it on camera.
はい、カメラに撮って
1 photo.
1枚写真
This is a student photo.
これ学生写真
This is fine.
これでいいじゃん
Her pussy is so beautiful though.
めちゃくちゃまんこきれいなんだけど
I have a small favor to ask of you.
ちょっとだけお願いがあるんだけど
A lifelong wish.
一生のお願いが
By yourself.
自分でね
That's the state.
その状態です
Spread it out.
広げてね
amazing.
すごい
It's all wet though.
びしゃびしゃですけど
It's easy to apply.
塗りやすいね
Isn't it the best?
最高じゃないか
hot.
熱い
Is your body temperature high?
体温高い?
I don't know what's inside my pussy.
自分のまんこの中とか分かんない
I get really wet when I laugh.
笑うとめちゃくちゃ湿るんですよ
Right?
でしょ?
When you laugh.
笑うとね
I can't move it at all.
ゆうゆう動かせないんだよ
amazing.
すごい
It's soaked
びしゃびしゃです
Yo.
よ
Butt here.
お 尻こっち
Upper Petan in the beginning.
序盤上ペターン
My butt started sticking out.
お尻つきだした
It looks like a woman's pussy.
諸女のまんこみたい
picture?
え?
Don't need the middle class period?
授業中期いらない?
You have a really beautiful pussy.
ほんと綺麗なまんこしてるね
How much do you want to see Monpan's uniform?
ど れくらいモンパンの制服が見たいんだよ
Sorry.
ごめんね
I've taken up a hobby.
趣味出しちゃって
In uniform.
制服姿
About a beautiful woman.
美人さんのこと
I want you to pat me nicely.
しっくりなでほしいな
Is it okay?
いいの?
You tried to let me go, right?
いかせようとしたでしょ?
Can I put it in here?
こっちに入れてもいい?
Should I turn this way?
こっち向ける?
Oh, it hurts.
おー、痛い
Looks like an old man.
おじさんてっちゃいそう
Can I take it out like this?
このまま出していい?
Can I cum inside you?
中出していい?
Let's go.
いくよ
Uncle also felt so good that he let out too much.
おじさんも気持ちよすぎて出しすぎちゃった
Be careful when communicating.
コミュニケーションは注意
If you go, my uncle will play it for you.
お じ さん行ってくれるとおじさんが流すから
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
It ends with my uncle making me feel good.
おじさんが気持ちよくしてもらって終わりにね
I'll clean it up a bit.
ちょっと きれいにしてあげるから
Good.
よいしょ
cold.
冷たい
cold?
冷たい?
Let's touch it in a disgusting way.
嫌らしい触り方しよう
I wish I had water.
水持ったらいいよ
Have you come to like me a lot?
だいぶ好きになったかな?
A lot.
だいぶ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Uncle will check.
おじちゃんがチェックになります
check?
チェック?
Down, down.
下、下
Let's go.
いくよ
Is that so?
そうなんの?
too
も
However, the stillness that I had expressed earlier might have come out.
しか したらさっき出した静止が出てきちゃったかもしれない
Why are you bursting out?
なんで吹き出そう?
Speech out.
吹き出す
Don't blow out the stillness inside.
中の静止を吹き出さないでね
Why are you bubbling up?
なんで吹き出すの?
this?
これ?
Would you like to do it again?
もう一回やらない?
One more time.
もう一回
good?
いい?
kind.
優しい
Can I take it out again?
また出していい?
good?
いい?